cacu.com 2009-12-31

# PRIVACY POLICY

We will partner only with businesses that follow strict
                                                                  PRIVACY
confidentiality requirements acceptable to the Credit Union
and by law. The businesses we select will offer products
designed to enhance your economic well being. Under no
                                                                  POLICY
circumstances will we authorize these firms to charge your
accounts without your expressed consent, and we will not
sell your information to telemarketing firms. Your account
numbers will not be disclosed.
It is important the information we maintain about you is
accurate and complete. If you see any information in your
monthly/quarterly statements that suggests our information
is incomplete or inaccurate, please write to P.O. Box 15950,
Lenexa, KS 66285-5950 or contact us at the numbers listed
on the front so we can update this information.
Protect Your Privacy Tips
We recognize the importance of our responsibility in
protecting your privacy. To assist you, we are providing the
following tips:
   • Use extreme caution, when disclosing your account
      number(s), social security number, etc., to others.
   • If someone calls you and explains that the call is on
      behalf of the Credit Union and asks for your account
      number, you should NOT disclose it. Our employees have
      access to your information and will not need to ask.
   • Keep all account numbers, card numbers, passwords
      and Personal Identification Numbers (PINs) in a
      protected place and separate from the card it offers
      access to (i.e., ATM, credit card or debit card). If the
      card is lost or stolen, the PIN could provide access to
      your card.
   • Maintain current information with the Credit Union
      (i.e., address and phone number). In case of fraudulent
      activity, this enables us to contact you immediately.
If you have comments or questions regarding this privacy
disclosure, please contact the Credit Union.
P.O. Box 15950, Lenexa, KS 66285-5950
800.892.7957
                                                                    800.892.7957 cacu.com
This credit union is federally insured by
the National Credit Union Administration.            CU-111 04-09

Protecting your personal information and using it in a         outside mailing for marketing purposes with which we have
manner consistent with your expectations is a high priority    a joint marketing agreement, companies offering products
for anyone associated with the Credit Union. We maintain       such as, life and term life insurance, accidental death and
physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect      dismemberment insurance, hospital accident protection
member information. We are required by law to provide you      insurance, vision and dental insurance and long-term
with a copy of our privacy policy at the time you become       care insurance and wellness insurances, vehicle service
a member or prior to your sharing of non-public personal       agreements, guaranteed auto protection agreements.
information with us and each year to explain how we collect,   Also, companies offering personal brokerage services,
use, and safeguard your personal financial information,        online brokerage services, life insurance and annuities,
therefore, we provide the following privacy disclosure:        trust services, privacy monitoring services, property and
                                                               casualty insurance, real estate services as well as legal
Information Collected and Disclosed About You
                                                               services contracts. All nonaffiliated companies that act on
We may collect nonpublic personal information about you        our behalf and receive Customer Information from us are
from the following sources:                                    contractually obligated to keep the information we provide to
                                                               them confidential, and to use the Customer Information we
   • Information that identifies you such as name, address,
                                                               share only to provide the services we ask them to perform.
     telephone number and social security number.
   • Information we received from you on applications or       Honoring Your Preferences
     other forms
                                                               You may request that we not share information with non-
   • Information about your transactions with us or others
                                                               affiliated third parties at any time. If you request that we
   • Information we receive from a consumer reporting
                                                               not share information with third parties, we may still share
     agency
                                                               information where permitted or required by law with our
   • Information obtained when verifying the information
                                                               service providers and with other financial companies with
     you provide on an application or other forms, such
                                                               whom we have joint marketing agreements.
     as from your current or past employers or from other
     institutions where you conduct financial transactions     You can tell us your preference by calling us toll-free
   • Information obtained from your computer access to our     at 1.800.892.7957 and talking to a member services
     website                                                   representative or by writing us at P.O. Box 15950, Lenexa,
                                                               KS 66285-5950.
We may disclose non-public personal information as
permitted by law. We do not disclose non-public personal       We will honor your request as soon as is reasonably
information about former members beyond the point at which     practicable. We will honor your preference until revoked by
membership terminates except as permitted by law. We           you in writing.
may disclose non-public personal information for purposes
                                                               We will protect your personal information. The Credit Union
of processing, servicing and recording transactions; with
                                                               will employ a security program to ensure the safety and
member’s consent; to protect the confidentiality of the credit
                                                               confidentiality of your records, protect against anticipated
union’s records; to protect against fraud; to comply with
                                                               threats or hazards to the security or integrity of such
state or federal law; to provide information to organizations
                                                               records, and protect against unauthorized access to or
involved in rating the credit union or assessing the credit
                                                               use of such records that could result in substantial harm
union’s standards; to consumer reporting agencies and
                                                               or inconvenience to you. Further, we restrict access of
to attorneys, accountants, auditors and regulators. We
                                                               nonpublic personal information about you to those employees
may disclose nonpublic personal information to companies
                                                               who need to know that information to provide products and
that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other
                                                               services to you.
financial institutions with which we have joint marketing
agreements.                                                    We will only share information when absolutely necessary.
                                                               We will only share information to administer the products
The categories of such companies to which we disclose the
                                                               and services we provide, when requested to do so by the
above referenced collected information include: Our affiliated
                                                               government, or when we partner with businesses to offer a
Credit Union Service Organization(s), companies performing
                                                               broader array of products and services.
